A Guide to the Department of Confederate Military Records, 1859-1996
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Unit Records
  - Subseries 3: Infantry
    - Regiments
      - 1st
        - Co. G (Gordon's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1861-1918 (Box 19, Folder 8)
        - Co. H (Richmond Greys, No. 2) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1879-1919 (Box 19, Folder 9)
        - Co. I (Morris' Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1879-1918 (Box 19, Folder 10)
        - Co. K (Virginia Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1861-1918 (Box 19, Folder 11)
        - Miscellaneous, 1906 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - 2nd
        - Co. A (Jefferson Guards), 1904 (Box 19, Folder 13)
        - Co. B (Hamtramck Guards), 1910-1913 (Box 19, Folder 14)
        - Co. C (Nelson Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1884 (Box 19, Folder 15)
        - Co. D (Berkeley Border Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1900-1914 (Box 19, Folder 16)
        - Co. E (Hedgesville Blues), n.d. (Box 19, Folder 17)
        - Co. F (Winchester Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 5), 1863-1906 (Box 19, Folder 18)
        - Co. G (Botts Greys), 1904 (Box 19, Folder 19)
        - Co. H (Letcher Riflemen), 1908-1919 (Box 19, Folder 20)
        - Co. I (Clarke Riflemen), 1904 (Box 19, Folder 21)
        - Co. K (Floyd Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1900-1919 (Box 19, Folder 22)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - 3rd
        - Co. A (Dismal Swamp Rangers), n.d. (Box 19, Folder 24)
        - Co. B (Virginia Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 3) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 5), 1862-1900 (Box 19, Folder 25)
        - Co. C (Dinwiddie Greys) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1884-1888 (Box 19, Folder 26)
        - Co. D (Southampton Greys), n.d. (Box 19, Folder 27)
        - Co. E (Cockade Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 5), 1861-1911 (Box 19, Folder 28)
        - Co. F (Nansemond Rangers), 1884-1905 (Box 19, Folder 29)
        - Co. G (Rough and Ready Guards), 1909-1993 (Box 19, Folder 30)
        - Co. H (National Greys), 1898 (Box 19, Folder 31)
        - Co. I (2nd) (James River Artillery), n.d. (Box 19, Folder 32)
        - Co. K (2nd) (Halifax Rifles), n.d. (Box 19, Folder 33)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 34)
      - 4th
        - Co. A (Wythe Grays), 1904-1914 (Box 19, Folder 35)
        - Co. B (Fort Lewis Volunteers), 1911 (Box 19, Folder 36)
        - Co. C (Pulaski Guards), 1904 (Box 19, Folder 37)
        - Co. D (Smyth Blues) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 5), 1864 (Box 19, Folder 38)
        - Co. E (Montgomery Highlanders), n.d. (Box 19, Folder 39)
        - Co. F (Grayson Dare Devils), n.d. (Box 19, Folder 40)
        - Co. G (Montgomery Fencibles), 1861-1913 (Box 19, Folder 41)
        - Co. H (Rockbridge Greys) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 5), 1863 (Box 19, Folder 42)
        - Co. I (Liberty Hall Volunteers), 1910 (Box 19, Folder 43)
        - Co. L (Newlee's Co.), 1909 (Box 19, Folder 44)
        - Miscellaneous, 1914 (Box 19, Folder 45)
      - 5th
        - Co. A (Marion Rifles), n.d. (Box 19, Folder 46)
        - Co. B (Rockbridge Rifles), n.d. (Box 19, Folder 47)
        - Co. C (Mountain Guard), 1911 (Box 19, Folder 48)
        - Co. D (Southern Guard), 1916 (Box 19, Folder 49)
        - Co. E (Augusta Grays), n.d. (Box 19, Folder 50)
        - Co. F (West View Infantry), n.d. (Box 19, Folder 51)
        - Co. G (Staunton Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1884 (Box 19, Folder 52)
        - Co. H (Augusta Rifles), 1910 (Box 19, Folder 53)
        - Co. I (Ready Rifles of Augusta Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1862-1906 (Box 19, Folder 54)
        - Co. K (Continental Morgan Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1900 (Box 19, Folder 55)
        - Co. L (West Augusta Guard), 1911 (Box 19, Folder 56)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 57)
      - 6th
        - Co. A (McKenney's Co.), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 1)
        - Co. B (2nd) (Princess Anne Grays), 1904 (Box 20, Folder 2)
        - Co. C (Woodis Rifles), 1912 (Box 20, Folder 3)
        - Co. D (Norfolk Light Infantry), 1912 (Box 20, Folder 4)
        - Co. E (2nd) (Nansemond Guards), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 5)
        - Co. F (Seaboard Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 5), 1912 (Box 20, Folder 6)
        - Co. G (Company F), 1861-1884 (Box 20, Folder 7)
        - Co. H (Independent Grays), 1912 (Box 20, Folder 8)
        - Co. I (Elliott Grays) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 5), 1862-1912 (Box 20, Folder 9)
        - Co. K (Alstadt Grays), 1904 (Box 20, Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - 7th
        - Co. A (Richardson Guards), 1903-1915 (Box 20, Folder 12)
        - Co. B (Washington Grays) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1884 (Box 20, Folder 13)
        - Co. C (Capt. John C. Porter's Co.), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 14)
        - Co. D (Giles Volunteers), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 15)
        - Co. E (Hazelwood Volunteers), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 16)
        - Co. G (Rappahannock Guard), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 17)
        - Co. H (Washington Volunteers), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 18)
        - Co. I (Holcombe Guards), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 19)
        - Co. K (Madison Grays), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 20)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - 8th
        - Co. A (Hillsborough Border Guard), 1906-1909 (Box 20, Folder 22)
        - Co. B (Piedmont Rifles), 1913-1915 (Box 20, Folder 23)
        - Co. C (Evergreen Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1884-1907 (Box 20, Folder 24)
        - Co. D (Champe Rifles), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 25)
        - Co. E (Hampton's Co.), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 26)
        - Co. F (Blue Mountain Boys), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 27)
        - Co. G (Thrift's Co.), 1889 (Box 20, Folder 28)
        - Co. H (Potomac Greys), 1910-1920 (Box 20, Folder 29)
        - Co. I (Simpson's Co.), 1884 (Box 20, Folder 30)
        - Co. K (Scott's Co.), 1913-1915 (Box 20, Folder 31)
        - Miscellaneous, 1906 (Box 20, Folder 32)
      - 9th
        - Co. A (Confederate Guard), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 33)
        - Co. B (Baltimore Artillery), 1916 (Box 20, Folder 34)
        - Co. C (Yellow Jacket Artillery), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 35)
        - Co. D (Virginia Artillery), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 36)
        - Co. E (Isle of Wight Blues), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 37)
        - Co. F (Phillip's Co.), 1910 (Box 20, Folder 38)
        - Co. G (Portsmouth Rifles), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 39)
        - Co. H (1st) (Lunenburg Heavy Artillery) (See Also Oversized - Box 3) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 5), 1861-1904 (Box 20, Folder 40)
        - Co. I (Craney Island Light Artillery), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 41)
        - Miscellaneous, 1904 (Box 20, Folder 42)
      - 10th
        - Co. A (Strasburg Guards), 1913 (Box 20, Folder 43)
        - Co. B (Rockingham Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1902-1912 (Box 20, Folder 44)
        - Co. C (1st) (Southern Grays) (See Also Oversized - Box 3) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 5), 1861-1913 (Box 20, Folder 45)
        - Co. D (Bridgewater Grays) (See Also Oversized - Box 3) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 5), 1861-1915 (Box 20, Folder 46)
        - Co. E (Peaked Mountain Grays) (See Also Oversized - Box 3) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 5), 1863-1900 (Box 20, Folder 47)
        - Co. F (Muhlenburg Rifles), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 48)
        - Co. G (Valley Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 3) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 5), 1862-1919 (Box 20, Folder 49)
        - Co. H (Chrisman's Infantry) (See Also Oversized - Box 3) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 5), 1862-1900 (Box 20, Folder 50)
        - Co. I (Riverton Invincibles) (See Also Oversized - Box 3) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 5), 1862-1900 (Box 20, Folder 51)
        - Co. K (Page Volunteers) (See Also Oversized - Box 3) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 5), 1862-1900 (Box 20, Folder 52)
        - Co. L (Jeff Davis Guards), 1863-1920 (Box 20, Folder 53)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 54)
      - 11th
        - Co. A (Lynchburg Rifle Greys) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 6), 1861-1912 (Box 20, Folder 55)
        - Co. B (Southern Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 3) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 6), 1861-1908 (Box 20, Folder 56)
        - Co. C (Clifton Greys), 1916 (Box 20, Folder 57)
        - Co. D (Fincastle Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1903 (Box 20, Folder 58)
        - Co. E (Lynchburg Rifles), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 59)
        - Co. F (Preston Guards), 1910 (Box 20, Folder 60)
        - Co. G (Lynchburg Home Guard), 1861-1877 (Box 20, Folder 61)
        - Co. H (Jeff Davis Guard), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 62)
        - Co. I (Rough and Ready Rifles), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 63)
        - Co. K (Valley Regulators) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1884-1894 (Box 20, Folder 64)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 65)
      - 12th
        - Co. A (Petersburg City Guard), 1899 (Box 21, Folder 1)
        - Co. B (Petersburg Greys, Co. A) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1899-1915 (Box 21, Folder 2)
        - Co. C (Petersburg Greys, Co. B), 1899-1916 (Box 21, Folder 3)
        - Co. D (Lafayette Guard), 1899-1911 (Box 21, Folder 4)
        - Co. E (Petersburg Riflemen) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1911-1912 (Box 21, Folder 5)
        - Co. F (Huger Greys) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1884-1911 (Box 21, Folder 6)
        - Co. G (Richmond Greys), 1907-1911 (Box 21, Folder 7)
        - Co. H (Norfolk Junior Volunteers), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 8)
        - Co. I (2nd) (Jones' Co.), 1912 (Box 21, Folder 9)
        - Co. K (Archer Rifles), 1899 (Box 21, Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous, 1904-1912 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - 13th
        - Co. A (Montpelier Guard), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 12)
        - Co. B (1st) (Culpeper Minute Men), 1900 (Box 21, Folder 13)
        - Co. C (Gordonsville Grays), 1916 (Box 21, Folder 14)
        - Co. D (Louisa Blues) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1905-1920 (Box 21, Folder 15)
        - Co. E (1st & 2nd) (Culpeper Riflemen) (Brandy Rifles), 1910-1911 (Box 21, Folder 16)
        - Co. F (Barboursville Guards), 1908 (Box 21, Folder 17)
        - Co. G (Lanier Guard), 1920 (Box 21, Folder 18)
        - Co. H (Fort Loudoun Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1884-1922 (Box 21, Folder 19)
        - Co. I (Frontier Rifles), 1911 (Box 21, Folder 20)
        - Co. K (Hampshire Guard), 1907 (Box 21, Folder 21)
        - Miscellaneous, 1864-1922 (Box 21, Folder 22)
      - 14th
        - Co. A (Paineville Rifles), 1884 (Box 21, Folder 23)
        - Co. B (Bedford Rifle Greys), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 24)
        - Co. C (Fluvanna Rifle Guard), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 25)
        - Co. D (Chesterfield Central Guards), 1906 (Box 21, Folder 26)
        - Co. E (Clarksville Blues) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 6), 1862 (Box 21, Folder 27)
        - Co. F (Chambliss Grays), 1914 (Box 21, Folder 28)
        - Co. G (1st) (Mount Vernon Guard) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 6), 1861 (Box 21, Folder 29)
        - Co. H (Meadville Grays), 1912 (Box 21, Folder 30)
        - Co. I (Chester Grays), 1913 (Box 21, Folder 31)
        - Co. K (Dan River Rifles) (See Oversized - Box 3) (See Oversized - Drawer 6), 1861-1884 (Box 21, Folder 32)
        - Miscellaneous, 1864-1914 (Box 21, Folder 33)
      - 15th
        - Co. A (Henrico Grays), 1864-1920 (Box 21, Folder 34)
        - Co. B (Virginia Life Guard) (See Also Oversized - Box 3) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 6), 1861-1906 (Box 21, Folder 35)
        - Co. C (Patrick Henry Rifles), 1861-1912 (Box 21, Folder 36)
        - Co. D (Henrico Guard), 1862-1910 (Box 21, Folder 37)
        - Co. E (Ashland Grays), 1899 (Box 21, Folder 38)
        - Co. F (Emmett Guard), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 39)
        - Co. G (Southern Guard), 1910 (Box 21, Folder 40)
        - Co. H (Young Guard), 1904 (Box 21, Folder 41)
        - Co. I (Hanover Grays), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 42)
        - Co. K (Marion Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1884 (Box 21, Folder 43)
        - Miscellaneous, 1860-1933 (Box 21, Folder 44)
      - 16th
        - Co. A (Marion Rangers), 1894-1906 (Box 21, Folder 45)
        - Co. B (Suffolk Continentals), 1906 (Box 21, Folder 46)
        - Co. C (Virginia Defenders), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 47)
        - Co. D (Isle of Wight Rifle Grays), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 48)
        - Co. E (Sussex Riflemen), 1903-1930 (Box 21, Folder 49)
        - Co. F (Fleet Rifle Guard), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 50)
        - Co. G (Atlantic Guard), 1895 (Box 21, Folder 51)
        - Co. H (1st) (Norfolk Light Artillery Blues) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 6), 1861 (Box 21, Folder 52)
        - Co. I (Manchester Artillery), 1902 (Box 21, Folder 53)
        - Co. K (Lee's Life Guard), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 54)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 55)
      - 17th
        - Field & Staff (See Oversized - Box 3), 1884 (Box 22, Folder 1)
        - Co. A (Alexandria Riflemen) (See Oversized - Box 3), 1884 (Box 22, Folder 2)
        - Co. B (Warren Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1861-1886 (Box 22, Folder 3)
        - Co. C (Loudoun Guard) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1884 (Box 22, Folder 4)
        - Co. D (Fairfax Riflemen) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1884-1889 (Box 22, Folder 5)
        - Co. E (Mount Vernon Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1884-1908 (Box 22, Folder 6)
        - Co. F (Prince William Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1884 (Box 22, Folder 7)
        - Co. G (Emmett Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1884 (Box 22, Folder 8)
        - Co. H (Old Dominion Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1884-1916 (Box 22, Folder 9)
        - Co. I (O'Connell Guards) (See Oversized - Box 3), 1884 (Box 22, Folder 10)
        - Co. K (Warrenton Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 3), 1861-1884 (Box 22, Folder 11)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - 18th
        - Co. A (Danville Blues), 1910 (Box 22, Folder 13)
        - Co. B (Danville Greys) (See Also Oversized - Box 4) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 6), 1861-1910 (Box 22, Folder 14)
        - Co. C (Nottoway Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 4) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 6), 1861-1915 (Box 22, Folder 15)
        - Co. D (Prospect Rifle Grays), 1906 (Box 22, Folder 16)
        - Co. E (Black Eagle Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 6), 1861 (Box 22, Folder 17)
        - Co. F (Farmville Guard), n.d. (Box 22, Folder 18)
        - Co. G (Nottoway Greys) (See Also Oversized - Box 4), 1878-1884 (Box 22, Folder 19)
        - Co. H (Appomattox Grays), 1907 (Box 22, Folder 20)
        - Co. I (Spring Garden Blues) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 6), 1862-1916 (Box 22, Folder 21)
        - Co. K (Charlotte Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 4) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 6), 1861-1921 (Box 22, Folder 22)
        - Miscellaneous, 1893-1931 (Box 22, Folder 23)
      - 19th
        - Co. A (Monticello Guard) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 6), 1862-1911 (Box 22, Folder 24)
        - Co. B (Albemarle Rifles), 1904 (Box 22, Folder 25)
        - Co. C (Scottsville Guard), n.d. (Box 22, Folder 26)
        - Co. D (Howardsville Grays), n.d. (Box 22, Folder 27)
        - Co. E (Piedmont Guards), n.d. (Box 22, Folder 28)
        - Co. F (Montgomery Guard), 1919 (Box 22, Folder 29)
        - Co. G (Nelson Grays) (See Also Oversized - Box 4), 1884-1885 (Box 22, Folder 30)
        - Co. H (Southern Rights Guard) (See Also Oversized - Box 4), 1884 (Box 22, Folder 31)
        - Co. I (Amherst Rifle Grays), 1884-1905 (Box 22, Folder 32)
        - Co. K (Blue Ridge Rifles), 1909 (Box 22, Folder 33)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 34)
      - 20th
        - Co. A (Virginia Guard), n.d. (Box 22, Folder 35)
        - Co. C (Stokes' Co.), 1861 (Box 22, Folder 36)
        - Co. D (Powhatan Rifles), 1861-1911 (Box 22, Folder 37)
        - Co. E (Lee Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 4), 1884-1904 (Box 22, Folder 38)
        - Co. G (Hampden-Sydney Boys), 1907 (Box 22, Folder 39)
        - Co. H (Clover Rifles), n.d. (Box 22, Folder 40)
        - Co. I (Brunswick Blues), n.d. (Box 22, Folder 41)
        - Miscellaneous (See Also Oversized - Drawer 6), 1861-1905 (Box 22, Folder 42)
      - 21st
        - Co. A (Red House Volunteers) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 7), 1861-1915 (Box 22, Folder 43)
        - Co. B (Maryland Guard), 1913 (Box 22, Folder 44)
        - Co. D (Cumberland Greys) (See Also Oversized - Box 4), 1884 (Box 22, Folder 45)
        - Co. E (Buckingham Leaches) (See Also Oversized - Box 4) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 7), 1861-1884 (Box 22, Folder 46)
        - Co. G (Robinson's Co.), 1907 (Box 22, Folder 47)
        - Co. H (Chalk Level Grays), 1904-1914 (Box 22, Folder 48)
        - Co. I (Turkey Cock Grays) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 7), 1861-1914 (Box 22, Folder 49)
        - Co. K (Meherrin Greys), 1861 (Box 22, Folder 50)
        - Miscellaneous, 1904-1916 (Box 22, Folder 51)
      - 22nd
        - Co. A (Border Rifles), 1916 (Box 22, Folder 52)
        - Co. B (Border Rifles), n.d. (Box 22, Folder 53)
        - Co. C (Mountain Cove Guards), n.d. (Box 22, Folder 54)
        - Co. D (Nicholas Blues), n.d. (Box 22, Folder 55)
        - Co. E (Elk River Tigers), n.d. (Box 22, Folder 56)
        - Co. F (Rocky Point Grays), 1913 (Box 22, Folder 57)
        - Co. G (Wyoming Riflemen) (See Also Oversized - Box 4), 1884 (Box 22, Folder 58)
        - Co. H (Kanawha Riflemen) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 7), 1861-1908 (Box 22, Folder 59)
        - Co. I (Boone Company), n.d. (Box 22, Folder 60)
        - Co. K (Fayetteville Rifles), n.d. (Box 22, Folder 61)
        - Miscellaneous, 1898 (Box 22, Folder 62)
      - 23rd
        - Co. A (Louisa Rifles), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 1)
        - Co. B (Jetersville Guards), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - Co. C (Amelia Rifles), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 3)
        - Co. D (Louisa Grays) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 7), 1861 (Box 23, Folder 4)
        - Co. E (Brooklyn Grays) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 7), 1861-1913 (Box 23, Folder 5)
        - Co. F (Goochland Grays) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 7), 1861 (Box 23, Folder 6)
        - Co. G (Frederick's Hall Grays) (See Also Oversized - Box 4) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 7), 1861-1910 (Box 23, Folder 7)
        - Co. H (Richmond Sharp Shooters), 1915 (Box 23, Folder 8)
        - Co. I (Central Guards), 1900 (Box 23, Folder 9)
        - Co. K (Keysville Guards), 1904-1921 (Box 23, Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous, 1905-1913 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - 24th
        - Co. A (Floyd Riflemen) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 7), 1861-1913 (Box 23, Folder 12)
        - Co. B (Hambrick's Co.), 1914-1916 (Box 23, Folder 13)
        - Co. C (Carroll Boys), 1904-1907 (Box 23, Folder 14)
        - Co. D (Taylor's Co.), 1913 (Box 23, Folder 15)
        - Co. E (Bentley's Co.), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 16)
        - Co. F (New River White Rifles), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 17)
        - Co. G (Richardson's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 4) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 7), 1861-1884 (Box 23, Folder 18)
        - Co. H (Henry Guards), 1884-1899 (Box 23, Folder 19)
        - Co. I (Lybrook's Co.), 1917 (Box 23, Folder 20)
        - Co. K (Hammet's Co.), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - 25th
        - Co. A (2nd) (Robinson's Co.), 1913 (Box 23, Folder 22)
        - Co. B (1st) (Rockbridge Guards) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 7), 1861 (Box 23, Folder 23)
        - Co. D (2nd) (Augusta Lee Rifles), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 24)
        - Co. E (1st) (Pendleton Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 4), 1900 (Box 23, Folder 25)
        - Co. F (2nd) (Highland Rangers), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 26)
        - Co. G (2nd) (Mollohan's Co.), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 27)
        - Co. H (1st) (Hardy Blues) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 7), 1861-1931 (Box 23, Folder 28)
        - Co. I (2nd) (Stofer's Co.), 1904-1913 (Box 23, Folder 29)
        - Co. K (2nd) (Pendleton Minute Men), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 30)
        - Miscellaneous, 1908-1914 (Box 23, Folder 31)
      - 26th
        - Co. A(York River Infantry) (See Also Oversized - Box 4), 1916 (Box 23, Folder 32)
        - Co. B (2nd) (Gloucester Grays) (See Also Oversized - Box 4) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 7), 1861-1916 (Box 23, Folder 33)
        - Co. C (King & Queen Minute Men) (See Also Oversized - Box 4) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 7), 1861-1908 (Box 23, Folder 34)
        - Co. D (James' Co.) (See Oversized - Box 4), 1884 (Box 23, Folder 35)
        - Co. E (Lincoln Hunters) (See Also Oversized - Box 4), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 36)
        - Co. F (Gloucester Invincibles) (See Also Oversized - Box 4), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 37)
        - Co. G (Clifton Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 4), 1884-1908 (Box 23, Folder 38)
        - Co. H (King & Queen Guards), 1908 (Box 23, Folder 39)
        - Co. I (Jackson Grays) (See Also Oversized - Box 4) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 7), 1862-1924 (Box 23, Folder 40)
        - Co. K (Easley's Co.), 1916 (Box 23, Folder 41)
        - Miscellaneous, 1861 (Box 23, Folder 42)
      - 27th
        - Co. A (Alleghany Light Infantry) (See Also Oversized - Box 4), 1905 (Box 23, Folder 43)
        - Co. B (Virginia Hibernians), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 44)
        - Co. C (Alleghany Rifles), 1916 (Box 23, Folder 45)
        - Co. D (Monroe Guard), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 46)
        - Co. E (Greenbrier Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 4), 1884 (Box 23, Folder 47)
        - Co. F (Greenbrier Sharp Shooters) (See Also Oversized - Box 4), 1884 (Box 23, Folder 48)
        - Co. G (Shriver Greys), 1898-1911 (Box 23, Folder 49)
        - Co. H (2nd) (Rockbridge Rifles), 1861-1919 (Box 23, Folder 50)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 51)
      - 28th
        - Co. A (Blue Ridge Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 5), 1884-1904 (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - Co. B (Craig Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 5), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 2)
        - Co. C (1st) (Old Dominion Rifles), 1913 (Box 24, Folder 3)
        - Co. C (2nd) (Craig Mountain Boys), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 4)
        - Co. D (Piedmont Rifles), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 5)
        - Co. E (3rd) (Botetourt Springs Rifles), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 6)
        - Co. F (Bedford Greys), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Co. G (Patty Layne Rifles), 1861-1911 (Box 24, Folder 8)
        - Co. H (Mountain Rifles), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 9)
        - Co. I (Deyerle's Co.) (Roanoke Grays), 1909-1912 (Box 24, Folder 10)
        - Co. K (Breckenridge Infantry), 1911 (Box 24, Folder 11)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - 29th
        - Co. A (McJessee's Co.), 1912-1914 (Box 24, Folder 13)
        - Co. B (Horne's Co.), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 14)
        - Co. C (Carroll Marksmen), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 15)
        - Co. D (Rifle Rangers), 1911-1913 (Box 24, Folder 16)
        - Co. E (Haynes' Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 5), 1911-1916 (Box 24, Folder 17)
        - Co. F (2nd) (March's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 5), 1884-1914 (Box 24, Folder 18)
        - Co. G (Smith's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 5), 1884 (Box 24, Folder 19)
        - Co. H (Bruster's Co.), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 20)
        - Co. I, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 21)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - 30th
        - Co. A (Fredericksburg Guard), 1884 (Box 24, Folder 23)
        - Co. B (Fredericksburg Rifle Grays), 1884 (Box 24, Folder 24)
        - Co. C (Gordon Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 5), 1884-1916 (Box 24, Folder 25)
        - Co. D (Mount Pleasant Rifles) (See Also Oversized - Box 5), 1903 (Box 24, Folder 26)
        - Co. E (Caroline Grays), 1904 (Box 24, Folder 27)
        - Co. F (Bowling Green Guards), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 28)
        - Co. G (Chilesburg Light Infantry), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 29)
        - Co. H (Sparta Grays) (See Also Oversized - Box 5), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 30)
        - Co. I (2nd) (Braxton's Co.), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 31)
        - Co. K (King George Grays) (See Also Oversized - Box 5), 1895-1905 (Box 24, Folder 32)
        - Miscellaneous, 1895-1912 (Box 24, Folder 33)
      - 31st
        - Co. A (Marion Guard), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 34)